<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation"> 
    <string-array name="help_list_qwe">        
        <item>Went out into a shop after sugar, returned with the basketful of foods, 
but. exactly buying sugar was forgotten. Acquainted? Then this application for you! 
By means of 2buy4 easily and quickly create simple shopping lists, 
distinguish to the category a color, copy lists, put checkoffs, 
send shopping lists by mail, scan коды of foods.</item>
        <item>Simpler can not be. Before a purchase create a new shopping list and in him 
you collect position. In a shop open this list and short tap you mark position.  </item>
        <item>Every shopping list consists of heading and positions. For an input new 
heading pass to the shopping list, press Plus in overhead part of form. 
Enter the name of new list. Choose any of 8 colors for a selection 
list. Shopping lists are shown in order of creation (in the beginning same 
new unfulfilled). If a list will be marked as executed, 
he automatically will be carried in an end. </item>
        <item>To copy a shopping list - long tap on the list, 
             menu select - Copy in the input box, enter the name 
             copies, and (if you want) a color, click Copy. In the new list will be 
             copied all the positions of the selected list.</item>
        <item>To modify header shopping list - long tap on the list, 
             menu select - Change. When you are prompted to make changes to the header 
             list.</item>
        <item>To delete a shopping list - long tap on the list, the menu 
             select - Delete. Deletes a list of his positions.</item>
        <item>Search on the shopping list is produced as a by name list 
             and the positions included in this list. To search, select 
             Menu - Search. In the search box, enter a value.</item>
        <item>To add items to the list - a short tap on the shopping list. 
             Viewer position list, click the Edit button 
             in the upper part of the screen. Input screen positions. 
             The left side of the screen is your shopping list. 
             Initially it is empty. In the right part of the screen is 
             list of products from which to choose values​​. 
             This list for selection may be formed by two 
             ways - using a built-in dictionary 
             apps and without it. On - off use 
             built-in dictionary - Dictionary button at the top right of the screen. 
             If the use of a dictionary is off, then the list for quick selection 
             will be offered only to those goods which have already been included in the 
             your shopping lists (including execution). Adding an entry 
             in position - a short tap on the list on the right or the button 
             Plus at the top of the screen. Some of the features you can input 
             set the position of one of 8 colors. Color for the product - this is an analogue product category. 
             Color on the shopping list is given as - long tap on the items in the left list. 
             Here you can change the name of the product or remove the product from the list. 
             Once you paint the products in different colors, the list to select 
             will also be displayed in accordance with these 
             (changes will take effect when you reopen the list of products). 
             Now, when your list has a different color, you can use 
             a filter for selecting the selection list by their color. Installation of the filter - short 
             tap the desired color color strip at the top of the screen. 
             Reset filter - white square with a cross.</item>
        <item>Shopping lists can be sorted by name, order entry, color. 
             To select the sort order in the shopping list screen, select 
             -Sort menu and set the desired order. Position within the shopping list is not sorted, 
             but simply displayed in the order purchased -> color line -> name </item>
        <item>A filter is used to reduce the number of records displayed 
             when choosing a new position or edit it. When you click in the upper 
             strip on the colored square, will set the filter of the corresponding color. 
             To reset the filter, click the box with a picture of the cross.</item>
        <item>Number of built-in dictionary is enabled by default. 
             Turns off and the dictionary pressing menu 
             Dictionary in the edit screen list.</item>
        <item>Select a shopping list, enter the screen position and performance of the mark 
             select Menu - Share with friends. Will generate a text message 
             containing the name of the list and the position in the list, indicating execution. </item>
        <item>Write to us - droidwelt@gmail.com We do not just design 
             mobile applications, automation of business - our 
             main activities, www.altamix.ru             </item>
   
    </string-array>
</resources>