<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation"> 
    <string-array name="news_list_ans">  
        <item> We have released a new program Google Play Shopping List PRO, which has a broader
             features compared with a simple shopping list. We recommend using it this compre
             program. Shopping List PRO also free and without advertising.            
        </item>      
        <item> In ToBuyFor PRO can create your own dictionaries, directories, add a group of products and units. 
		       For shopping, you can specify the quantity, price, value, view the history of price shopping. 
			   Widget application will show you all of the latest shopping lists. You can customize the animation 
			   display screens and select one of the five themes of the application. Now you can transfer the 
			   application database (by means of a file manager Android) to other devices</item>
        <item> Adjust the dictonary, his group and units and makes any shopping lists - from weekly purchases 
		       in the hypermarket to the estimates for the repair of an apartment or a car. Ask the quantity and 
			   price of the position -The cost will be calculated automatically When you enter a position, 
			   you can calculate the price by the quantity and value of the position or the number of 
			   through price and cost. Do not remove the old lists - just mark it as done, and then you can 
			   trace the history of changes in the purchase price. At the level of purchased items 
			   at the bottom of the list shows the remaining amount of the purchase - you can always orient, 
			   there will be enough money to buy. Making lists on a trip on vacation or a business trip, 
			   the price is specified under the weight position, and you end up with the weight of your luggage. 
			   Choose a theme for your application preferences and mood, use the application with pleasure!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>